macroholding.com 2017-10-07

# Privacy – Macro Holding

Macro Holding is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Macro Holding Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Macro Holding website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Macro Holding collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Macro Holding also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal address, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Macro Holding. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Macro Holding for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Macro Holding Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Macro Holding public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Macro Holding does not read any of your private online communications.

Macro Holding encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Macro Holding so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Macro Holding is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Macro Holding and Macro Holding family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

Macro Holding collects and uses your personal information to operate the Macro Holding Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Macro Holding also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Macro Holding and its affiliates. Macro Holding may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Macro Holding does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Macro Holding may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Macro Holding may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Macro Holding, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Macro Holding keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Macro Holding, in order to determine what Macro Holding services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Macro Holding to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Macro Holding Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Macro Holding or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Macro Holding; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Macro Holding, or the public.

Withdrawing Your Consent

You may notify us at any time that you wish to withdraw or change your consent to our use and disclosure or your information. We will accommodate your request subject to legal and contractual restrictions related to your transactions. If you have “opted in” or subscribed to one of our newsletters or mailing lists, we will always provide you the opportunity to “opt out” or unsubscribe. For example, each e-newsletter we send to you will include a link or other method to unsubscribe or decline further e-newsletters.

Use of Cookies

The Macro Holding Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Macro Holding pages, or register with Macro Holding site or services, a cookie helps Macro Holding to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Macro Holding Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Macro Holding features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Macro Holding services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Macro Holding secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Macro Holding secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

Macro Holding will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Macro Holding encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Macro Holding is protecting your information.
